A Guide to the Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File FA1087
Rockefeller Archive Center
Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File
1953-1990
1970-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Lederberg, Joshua
Rockefeller University
FA1087
74.4 Cubic Feet 62 standard record storage boxes.
Arrangement
As received.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 305-1-U
Scope and Contents
This collection comprises Lederberg's personal subect files primarily documenting his interests and activities outside that of Rockefeller University including but not limited to: Cetus Corporation, Recombinant DNA, the Human Frontier Science Program, National Science Foundation (NSF), National Cancer Institute (NCI), National Resources Defense Council, Annual Reviews, Inc., Institute for Scientific Information (ISI), National Academy of Science (NAS), and his work with NASA, particularly the Viking Mission to Mars. The collection also includes select subject files from Rockefeller University as well as his work at Stanford University.
Biographical / Historical
Joshua Lederberg was most prominantly known for his work in the fields of molecular biology, artificial intellegence, exobiology, human rights advocacy, as well as his science and public policy advisory to nine U.S. Presidents, and his prominent role with the National Aeuronautics Space Administration (NASA) missions to Mars.
For his work with genetic transfer among bacteria Lederberg shared the 1958 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine with Edward Tatum and George Beadle. For his lifetime of achievement Lederberg was also recognized with the 1989 National Medal of Science and the 2006 Presidential Medal of Freedom.
For a detailed biography of Joshua Lederberg, please see the Rockefeller University "Awards and Honors" website.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection is restricted pending permission from Rockefeller University.
- Subject File, 1
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1-45)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1979 April-August (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
  - Cetus Corporation - Dog Food, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cetus Corporation - Vitamin (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cetus Corporation - History (Includes Lederberg's Preliminary Draft on the Use of Methods of Genome Disection and Gene Transportation) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cetus Corporation - DNA Splicing, 1975 March-June (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1974 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Bio 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation - Protein Uses, DNA Insert, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cetus Corporation - Genetic Insertion Plan (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - Cetus Corporation - Scientific Laboratories Business Plan, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Cetus Corporation - Brochure (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cetus Corporation - Res Management, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cetus Corporation - Draft Letter, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cetus Corporation - Lederberg's Comments (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cetus Corporation - Laboratories, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cetus Corporation - Syntex (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cetus Corporation - Research and Development Organizations (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cetus Corporation - Contracts, 1973 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cetus Corporation - Bill - 1973 - Expenses (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973 August-September (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1974 December (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cetus Corporation - Miscellaneous - 1975 January, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cetus Corporation - Steroids, 1975 March (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cetus Corporation -Manuscript (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cetus Corporation - Enrichment Cultures (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cetus Corporation - Union Carbide (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Electric (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cetus Corporation - Regs, Growth (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cetus Corporation - N-Fixation (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cetus Corporation - Energy - Miscellaneous, 1975 January (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cetus Corporation - Computer, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1974 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1974 November (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cetus Corporation - Env. Ideas (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1974 August (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cetus Corporation - (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cetus Corporation - Ascatopics (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Cetus Corporation - Cell Culture (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Cetus Corporation - Management Planning (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cetus Corporation - Energy Resources (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cetus Corporation - Coal, Oil (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cetus Corporation - 1973 - Steroids and Stacophylococcus Aureus (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Oil Microbial (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cetus Corporation - NCI (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cetus Corporation - Agr. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cetus Corporation - Asca, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cetus Corporation - Fermentation Econ. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Microbial US-USSR, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cetus Corporation - Metabolic Regualtiuon, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cetus Corporation - Library (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Cetus Corporation - Ferm. Engineering (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Enzyme Engineering as Related to Food and Energy Production, University of California-San Diego, 1974 July 22-25 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Wischneski, U. - Thermochemical Processes and Cycles, 1974 December 10 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Marine Meal Binding, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Enzyme Engineering (Box 3, Folder 13A)
  - Flotation (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - USI, 1977 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 16-34)
  - Chemicals for Coal and Shale - and Research and Development Analysis for National Science Foundation, 1975 July (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Octagon Papers, 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1-6)
  - Inner Ear (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cetus Corporation - Reprints, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cetus Corporation - Reprints - Antibiotics (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 May-October (Box 4, Folder 10-19)
  - Cetus Corporation - Mushrooms, 1976 September 8 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 April-November (Box 4, Folder 21-36)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1976 April (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 March-May (Box 5, Folder 2-8)
  - Cetus Corporation - Bylinsky (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cetus Corporation - Demain, A. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Streptokinase (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Automation Aub Assay (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973 August 29 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cetus Corporation - Mutagenesis (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation - Systems Engineering (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Cetus Corporation - Minutes (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cetus Corporation - Ciba Geigy (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cetus Corporation - Staff (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cetus Corporation - Phages (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cetus Corporation - Lab Routine (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cetus Corporation - Sterility (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lilly-Ceph Patent (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cetus Corporation - New Antibiotic (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Cetus Corporation - Micromonospora (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Clapper, Wm. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Nitrate Efforts (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Bradford - Wool Type Card (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Unavailable. Removed from collection.
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 January-February (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Statistics (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 January-February (Box 5, Folder 31-34)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bio RFP-NIH (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1976 January-February (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Cetus Corporation - Agenda for Scientific Meeting, 1975 October 1 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Raymond Notes (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 August, October-December (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Cetus Corporation - Notes (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 September-November (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - A Technology Assessment Methodology (Enzymes) Industrial, 1971 June (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1975 July (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cetus Corporation - Fructose (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 October (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cetus Corporation - Yeast (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 June-September (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Biosphere as a Long-Range Investment (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 February, June-September (Box 6, Folder 14-17)
  - Cetus Corporation - Immunoglobulins, 1975 September (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cetus Corporation - DNA Phase, 1975 April 27 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cetus Corporation - Immunassay (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Cetus Corporation - Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Biophore Plan (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cetus Corporation - Schering Antibiotic (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cetus Corporation - Schering, 1973 March 14 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Cetus Corporation - Gentamicin, 1973 January-February (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Cetus Corporation - NY Ethyl Corp, 1973 September 28 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Cetus Corporation - Demain, A. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Cetus Corporation (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Cetus Corporation - Sickle Screen, 1973 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Cetus Corporation - Readings (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Cetus Corporation - Business Plan, 1972 March (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 35-43)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1-6)
  - Cetus Corporation - Scientific Meeting VI, 1986 January 12-16 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1985 April-December (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Cetus Corporation - Pioneer (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cetus Corporation - Bact Cellulose (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Annual and Quarterly Reports, Financial Statements (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cetus Corporation - Flukes (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Library (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation - Computer Oracle, 1981 May (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Cetus Corporation - Dr. Ronald B. Cape - Cetus Scientific Lab (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation - Financial Statements (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1978 June, August-September (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
  - Cetus Corporation - Library Request, 1978 August (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1978 July-August (Box 7, Folder 20-25)
  - B-12 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1977-1978 June (Box 8, Folder 3-9)
  - Cetus Corporation - Alcohol, Biomass, Coal, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Cetus Corporation - Amoco (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Schering, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Polypeptides (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1977 November 21 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - B-12 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1977 May, July-December (Box 8, Folder 17-24)
  - Cetus Corporation - Library (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cetus Corporation - B-12 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SCP-USSR (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Proponate (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1977 March-1978 March (Box 8, Folder 29-33)
  - 1975 - Cellulose (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 35-40)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1978 April-May (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cetus Corporation - Articles (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1977 March-June (Box 9, Folder 3-7)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1985 July-December (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Cetus Corporation - Current, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1983 May, July (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Cetus Corporation - Turkey (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cetus Corporation, 1983 June 12-16 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cetus Corporation - Personnel, Payroll, Misc. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 16-19)
  - Cetus Corporation - PIO (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cetus Corporation - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - Cetus Corporation - Scientific Meeting, 1980 October 23-30 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Cetus Corporation - Scientific Meeting, 1981 December 8-13 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Cetus Corporation - Asilomar (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cetus Corporation - Biochip (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Cetus Corporation - Biophore, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Cetus Corporation - Fructose, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Cetus Corporation - J. Harrison - Heart Disease, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Cetus Corporation - Bio Wax, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cetus Corporation - Immune - Peptides, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cetus Corporation - Technical Newsletter, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cetus Corporation - Biomass, Miscellaneous, Foodstuffs, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1979 February-March (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cetus Corporation - General Correspondence, 1978 December-1981 November (Box 10, Folder 1-13)
  - Cetus Corporation - Vitamin, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Cetus Corporation - Plant Biology (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cetus Corporation - Corp. Ethanol (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Health Service Research - NSF Proposal, 1977 August (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Health Service Research - Seminars, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Health Service Research - Seminars, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Committee Health Services Research Center, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Bibliography (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Candidates (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Newsletter (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Short List (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Personnel (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - U. E. Reinhardt (Candidate) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Publications (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Health Services Administration (HSA) Program (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Rejected, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Confidential material
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Rejected, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Rejected, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University - Applications and Inquiries - Graduate Work, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Negative, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Negative, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University - Applications and Inquiries, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University - Applications (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University - Applications, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Student Applications - Negative, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Student Inquiries, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Applications - Negative, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University - Graduate Student Applications, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ikle Commission, 1987 April 30 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - General Correspondence, 1987 September, November (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS), 1987 September 11 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Heart of the Matter (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - Minutes, 1987 July (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - Soviety Bureaucratic Politics - Charles H. Fairbanks, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS), 1987 March-May (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - MCC Software and Technology Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10-15)
  - Ikle Commission, 1987 February 20 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ikle Commission (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ikle San Diego Seminar, 1987 August 24-28 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - Articles (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - General Correspondence, 1987 July-August (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - Table of Appendices, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy (CILS) - General Correspondence, 1987 August (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - RD, 1986 July 7 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - MacArthur CIF Government Advisory (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - MacArthur BW (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Learning and US-Nye (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - MacArthur Foundation - General Correspondence, 1986 September-December (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - CIF Corrections, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - International Peace and Security-MacArthur (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Mac Exp (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - MacArthur CIF, 1986 January-June (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - MacArthur CIF, 1985 April-December (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
  - MacArthur Foundation - Miscellaneous Readings - CIF (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - MacArthur Foundation - Meeting, 1986 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Recombinant DNA - Campbell and Perkins - DNA-EPA, 1977 January 26 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1977 April-November (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Recombinant DNA - Articles, 1977 April-June (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Recombinant DNA - WHO-Bogell Sgaramells-Ehrlich, 1977 June (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Recombinant DNA - Senate Bills (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1977 February-April (Box 13, Folder 7-10)
  - Department of Education and Scientific (London) - Report of the Working Party on the Practice of Genetic Manipulation (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1977 April-October (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - NRDF - re: Recombinant DNA Research, 1976 November 17 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Recombinant DNA - Carstens, A. S., 1976 November 11 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Recombinant DNA - Asilomar (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Recombinant DNA - McCullough, James M. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Recombinant DNA - Asilomar (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Recombinant DNA - HR 7418 - To Regulate Activities of DNA (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Recombinant DNA - IBM Lecture - Gene Splicing, 1976 March (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Recombinant DNA - WHO 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Recombinant DNA - Current Guidelines for Research on Recombinant DNA Molecules, 1975 September (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Recombinant DNA - Kutter, Betty - Draft Version of NIH Recombinant DNA Guidelines (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Recombinant DNA - DNA Biohazards (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Recombinant DNA - Asilomar, 1975 February 24-27 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Recombinant DNA - Morgan J. - Trends in Biochem Science, 1976 April 21 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Recombinant DNA - Bowers, Bert (Syntex), 1976 June 22 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Recombinant DNA - Bowers, A. (Syntex), 1976 October 4 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Recombinant DNA - Meeting Recombinant DNA Molecule, 1975 February 25 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Recombinant DNA - Grobstein, Clifford, 1976 September 10 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1976 July-August (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Recombinant DNA - Lederberg, S. - The Least Hazardous Course - Recombinant DNA as an Option for Human Genetic, Viral and Cancer Therapy (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Recombinant DNA - DNA-Guidelines-Comments (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Recombinant DNA - Stanford - DNA Patent, 1976 July 7 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1976 May-June (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Recombinant DNA - Guidelines - De W. Stetter (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Recombinant DNA - General Correspondence, 1976 February-August (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Recombinant DNA - Curtiss, Roy, 1976 April 12 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Recombinant DNA - NCI - Recombinant DNA (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Recombinant DNA - Moore, Gregory, 1975 May 12 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Recombinant DNA - Lewis, Andrew (NIH) - Statement Submitted to Berg Committee, 1975 March 6 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Recombinant DNA - Asilomar Conference, 1975 February 24-27 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Recombinant DNA - Biophore Propoganda, 1975 June (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Recombinant DNA - Young, Frank - Statement on the Use of B Subtilis in Recom Molecule Technology, 1975 November 12 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1975 August-1976 February (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Recombinant DNA - Bio Hazard NIH NARSM (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Recombinant DNA - Helinski, D. R. (University of California-San Diego, 1976 February 6 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Recombinant DNA - NIH, 1976 February 9 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1977 February-March (Box 13, Folder 49-50)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 51-52)
  - Recombinant DNA - NIH Environmental Impact Statement, 1976 Seotember 2 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Recombinant DNA - NIH, 1976 July 20 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1976 May-1977 January` (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Recombinant DNA - NIH, 1976 June (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Recombinant DNA (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Recombinant DNA - Articles (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Recombinant DNA - June 13, 1977 - Friedlein, Zinder and Javitz, 1977 June 13 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Japan (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Erato (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Suntory (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - RU - Japan (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Suntory (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Japan Science Foundation (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Japan - Senator Bentsen-D. Deane - March 2, 1988 in Washington, 1988 March 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Two Decades of Progress - The US-Japan Cooperative Medical Science Program, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NAS Feasibility Study-Japan (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Human Frontier Science Program (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - CPR - Japan, 1985 June 20 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Japan - News Clippings (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Japan Trip, 1985 November 11-19 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hamamatsu Photonics (Box 14, Folder 14)